(Amy:)You know, I'm sorry your
mother made you feel bad.
(Amy:)But, you know, at the end
of the day, she was wrong,
(Amy:)because you're not alone.
(Sheldon:)You're right.
(Sheldon:)I have Leonard
and Howard and Raj,
(Sheldon:)Stuart, Penny,
(Sheldon:)Leonard's mom, Bernadette,
Wil Wheaton...
(Amy:)What about the woman who just
buttered your big flat feet?
(Sheldon:)I was going chronologically.
(Sheldon:)You're right between
Koothrappali's father
(Sheldon:)and Omar, the one-eyed
Sparkletts guy.
(Amy:)Well, let's try to not let it
ruin the rest of our trip.
(Sheldon:)I knew we should've
never mentioned
(Sheldon:)us living together
in the first place.
(Amy:)She was gonna find out
eventually.
(Sheldon:)Disagree.
(Sheldon:)We've known about evolution
since 1859.
(Sheldon:)She still believes in Noah
and his amazing zoo boat.
(Sheldon:)This could have all been avoided
(Sheldon:)if you'd only listened to me.
(Leonard:)Sheldon,
(Amy:)I knew your mother was fine
with us living together
(Amy:)because I already
told her we were.